In the CLO, use the template to build the model.
Like these three small cube.
Take it out as OPT.
Then put this OPT into the name line to use.
Be careful before you export.
Put the model in place first.
It is placed in the middle like this now.
Put it on the floor and check it in the 3D window.
Does it show the floor grid?
Find the X-axis according to the floor grid.
The name line will repeat along the X-axis.
Refer to this picture.
This is the direction of the three axes in the 3D window.
Go back to the software.
Press the shortcut 5 to switch to the 5-angle.
In the case of the 5-angle, the X-axis is horizontal.
The name line will follow the blue, red, and yellow.
Press the shortcut 5 to switch to the 5-angle.
Then export it to OPT.
In the menu bar, export, OPT.
Select an address.
Save it to the desktop first.
Remember the name.
This is the export OPT window.
Let's take a look at the information in here.
You can watch this video about the settings of the export OPT.
I won't talk about all the options in here.
Let's set it directly.
Set a single target.
The thick one.
Click on the unified UV coordinates.
As long as the slow shooting picture is OK.
The發現 picture is not needed.
Then go down.
Save it with the text file.
Just save it as a compressed package.
Click OK.
The compressed package after export is on the desktop.
Right-click to unzip.
Open the file after unzipping.
You can see the corresponding OPT file.
Go back to the software.
Open the file of this skirt.
Next, complete the strap of this skirt.
Switch to the thick texture surface.
Turn off the display of the inner line and the basic line.
Zoom in to see the model shoulder.
Create a new name line.
Click add.
The OPT name line window will appear.
The left side is the corresponding setting.
The right side is the preview window.
It's still empty at this time.
You need to add the OPT file first.
See here.
There is a browse button.
Click the browse button.
Open the OPT file just exported.
The length and width of the display is the size of the OPT file.
And it appears in the preview window.
At this time, its scale is 0.
The scale refers to the distance between each OPT unit.
When exporting before.
Three small objects are exported together.
Then they are a unit.
After modifying the scale to 10mm.
The distance between three small objects and the next group of small objects.
Changed to 10mm.
The scale is changed to 0.
See this part above.
Here you can modify the ratio.
The rotation of the axis can make the OPT.
Rotate on the axis of X, Y, and Z.
Here you don't need to select.
Because we have already set it at the beginning.
Now just import it directly.
Modify the settings.
The scale refers to the number of lines we have added.
The distance between the inner line and the outer line of the board.
Changed to 0.
Use the free line tool.
Add the number of lines to the board.
The number of lines added is gray.
Because the corresponding UV image has not been added yet.
Select the number of lines at the object window.
Then click the browse button at the back of the text.
Add the UV image.
The rest of the shoulder boards are also added to the number of lines.
Finally, hide the bottom sheet.
Click the fabric used for the shoulder board.
Change the opacity of the fabric to 0.
The surface is now clean.
The surface of the fabric is now clean.
The surface of the board is now clean.